字幕为自制
字幕样式部分来自EQCN，部分修改自潮汐字幕社
翻译来自EQCN
本字幕采用知识共享-署名-相同方式共享 4.0 国际许可协议进行许可
http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/deed.zh
All right, everypony
好了， 各位小马
We are here to celebrate the birthday
今天这一场庆生派对
and anniversary...
还有周年庆...
of Rainbow Dash
开给云宝黛西
Hey, everypony
大家好啊
Who's ready to get their party on
谁准备好来一起狂欢了吗
Hit it
唱起来
Get your hooves up, party's starting out right now
马蹄飞扬 派对热闹起来
Everypony, everypony get down
大家一起涌入欢乐海洋
Time to make a wish, better make it right now
许下愿望 不要错过机会
It's been a year and today is your birthday party
庆祝周年 庆祝你的生日派对
Make a wish, it's your birthday
许个愿 在这生日会
Make a wish, it's your birthday party
许个愿 在这生日派对
Make a wish, it's your birthday
许个愿 在这生日会
Make a wish, it's your birthday party
许个愿 在这生日派对